[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Yes, since the last time I saw you, I thought you would never invite me back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Chateau le Tour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Yes, it's a Chateau le Tour.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Are they called the Fallonettes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "They are not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "How do you jump this rock star shot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Thanks, god.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 60, "question": "The new look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "The new look -- I'm just losing --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Are you not taken so seriously as a rock star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I just have this compilation of all this music and maybe it is going in my ahead a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Bruce Springsteen, I mean incredibly, you got him to cover Willis Smith's hit, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "\"Whip My Hair.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce Springsteen", "Willis Smith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "-- The Boss?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "The Boss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Is he serious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "And it's like, if you think about it, when would he -- when would he ever see Bruce dressed like he was 30 years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Listen, it's a brilliant album.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "How did you persuade him to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "It was one of these weird things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 208, "question": "It's just the joy of competition, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Or did you deliberately lose to her to try and get the --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "-- with the president?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "No, because we did everything inside the White House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "CC", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 224, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think you're enhancing the reputation of your nation and its great leader by doing a sack race the East Room, a potato race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, the goal of this is to get children to get fit and workout and do --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Room"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "And you had a private meeting with the president before this -- the slow jam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 241, "question": "How does that go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, the -- it's -- by protocol, they want you to meet the president alone, because you invited him, so you -- so I'm -- I have to be there in -- no -- no stage manager, no assistants, no Fallonettes, no one is allowed to --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 381, "question": "-- who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "-- why would I impersonate someone with three minutes left --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "I want to show God my act?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Don't be so American literal about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Can you get more index cards laid out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "So this \"Call Me Maybe,\" even my kids back in England, who wouldn't necessarily know who you are, now know you're the guy from the \"Call Me Maybe\" clip, because two million hits on YouTube.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Would you turn down the \"Tonight Show\" if you were offered it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "No, I wouldn't turn it down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Is it -- is it the Holy Grail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "ALLON: I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Hasn't it always been the Holy Grail as a -- as a talk show host in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I think it's the story around it, but it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "What is the kind of interview that absolutely sends you demented?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "It's -- they Google.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "What do you think of America right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "You're starting right off there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "How much has that guided your sense of people not being reliant on their parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "That's a really good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Are you an Obama man at heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What is the kind of leader that you're craving in an American president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Moral compass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Do you want to name how many you've rolled in the hay with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "More than one and less than five.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Did you actually roll in the hay with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "She actually has a hay bale in her bedroom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Why shouldn't their opinion, their Tweets be as valuable to the world as yours or mine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "I have no problem with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'90s"]}, "docId": "120623pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", ":", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "What do you feel about this album?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "What's interesting about it in my life is I made some great albums in the '90s and -- which become sort of almost like a mill stone around my neck.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]